# File that stores the quiz data - questions and answer list in a nested dictionary/list data structure
question_data = [
    {"text": "A slug's blood is green.", "answer": "True"},
    {"text": "The loudest animal is the African Elephant.", "answer": "False"},
    {"text": "Approximately one quarter of human bones are in the feet.", "answer": "True"},
    {"text": "The total surface area of a human lungs is the size of a football pitch.", "answer": "True"},
    {"text": "In West Virginia, USA, if you accidentally hit an animal with your car, "
             "you are free to take it home to eat.", "answer": "True"},
    {"text": "In London, UK, if you happen to die in the House of Parliament, you are entitled to a state funeral.",
     "answer": "False"},
    {"text": "It is illegal to pee in the Ocean in Portugal.", "answer": "True"},
    {"text": "You can lead a cow down stairs but not up stairs.", "answer": "False"},
    {"text": "Google was originally called 'Backrub'.", "answer": "True"},
    {"text": "Buzz Aldrin's mother's maiden name was 'Moon'.", "answer": "True"},
    {"text": "No piece of square dry paper can be folded in half more than 7 times.", "answer": "False"},
    {"text": "A few ounces of chocolate can to kill a small dog.", "answer": "True"}
]

new_data = [{"category": "General Knowledge",
             "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
             "question": "Coca-Cola's original colour was green.",
             "correct_answer": "False",
             "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
            {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
             "question": "The sum of all the numbers on a roulette wheel is 666.",
             "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
            {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
             "question": "An eggplant is a vegetable.", "correct_answer": "False",
             "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
            {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
             "question": "Cucumbers are usually more than 90% water.",
             "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
            {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
             "question": "The average woman is 5 inches ~ 13 centimeters shorter than the average man.",
             "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
            {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
             "question": "The term 'Spam' came before the food product 'Spam'.",
             "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
            {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
             "question": "Sitting for more than three hours a day can cut two years off a person's life expectancy.",
             "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
            {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
             "question": "The French word for 'glass' is 'glace'.",
             "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
            {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
             "question": "Albert Einstein had trouble with mathematics when he was in school.",
             "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
            {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
             "question": "Haggis is traditionally ate on Burns Night.",
             "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}
            ]
